私どもに名前を持つ 許しを頂けませぬか？ 「名前」とは何だ？ 記号のようなものでございます
With the detonation of Miniature Rose,
the bomb activated by the stopping of his heart, Netero perished with the King.
ＮＧＬねぇ。
But damn it...
何でもかんでも　自然のままの 生活がいいと思ってる。
We must hurry... Or it'll
be too late for the King!
そんなとこに住んでる奴らも 物好きなら 訪れる　あんた達も物好きだな。
And there isn't time to take him to Pitou!
何があるんだか知らねえが 今日だけで
It will be fine...
あんた達みたいな連中を １０組くらい乗せて来たぜ。
I will save the King.
１０組も？ ああ。
How?
俺達は　むしろ 後発組だったようだな。
I will feed myself to him...
でも　本当にいるのかな？ 人間を襲うほどの 大きな虫なんて…。
Come, my cells!
もちろん　常識じゃ考えられない。 でも　あいつらが聞いたという あの無線機からの声…。
Diffuse throughout the King and heal him!
南西方面　ＭＡ１８地区に
Your Majesty...
新たな人間の村を 発見したということだ。
Are you all right?
戸数１２ 推定居住人数は　２０６０体。
How do you feel? This exquisite taste...
まだ　そんな村が残ってたんだ。
I feel as though I am breathing the air of paradise.
そっちは　おおかた 取り尽くしたと思ってたけどね。 早速　この村を 本日の攻撃目標に組み入れる。
My strength is returning...
コルト　行ってくれるか？ 了解。
This is a fairy mist.
何だよ　ペギー 俺じゃねえのかよ。 ヂートゥは　当初の予定通り 北西部を担当してもらいたい。
I am...
ザザンも同様。 北西部には　もう　大した村は 残ってないんじゃないの？
I am not worthy of such praise!
逃げ回るのを取っ捕まえるのが 面白いのに！ ヂートゥ！　狩りは　遊びではない。
I am happy to hear that.
女王様への奉仕だ。
Please feast to your heart's content.
我々は　決められた数の人間を きっちり捕らえて来ればよい。
There is plenty here.
分かってるって　コルト！ 仕事は　きっちりやるよ。 なぁ？　ザザン！
I crave it...
決められたノルマは守るわよ。 でも　狩りの方法まで 指図されたくないわ。 私は私で勝手にやる。 逃げ回る人間を狩るのは やっぱり楽しいもの。 何だと？
Now that I have experienced this taste, I cannot eat anything else...
適当に息抜きしながら やったほうが
Your Majesty...
仕事は　うまく行くっていうぜ！
Your Majesty, Your Majesty, Your Majesty!
何が勝手にだ。 師団長が　あれでは 兵に示しがつかん！ それぞれ名前を持ったのは
Please stop taking me to the heights
of heaven's bliss with your praise!
軍の統率にとっては 便利であったが
No more!
その問題が軍紀の緩みにも つながりかねん。
Your Majesty!
早めに手を打たねば。
確かに　引き締め策は必要だな。 この師団長会議にも
You may also feed on this.
ユンジュは　どこだ？ なぜ来ない！ ほら　やっぱり怒る だから嫌なんだぜ。
He's liquefying his cells.
何でも俺のせいにされるし…。 隠せば　お前も罪に問われる それでも…。
You thought this through, Youpi.
ユンジュの奴　そいつら　みんな
It's so powerful and rich...
ペットにするんだって 息巻いてたぜ？
Surely, this comes from the heavens.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。 うわ！
Drops of angels themselves...
踏んじまったじゃねえか！ もっと私達を 楽しませてちょうだい！
Your Majesty!
ホッ　ホッ　ホッ…！ ハッハッハ…。 死ぬ気で逃げろよ！
There is no way to compare the two.
死ぬまでなぁ…　フフフ…。
All I can say is that I have never tasted better...
あの２本の　デッケェ木が 検問所　兼　大使館さ。
Not enough... I need more.
ああ　こんな　辺ぴな所に 何があるんだか まったく　物好きな連中だぜ。
Bring me as much as you can of both...
アリの前にＮＧＬも題目通りの エコ団体じゃないからな。
Yes!
分かってる。
My King!
どのようなご用件で？
With pleasure!
ハントだ。
Supreme bliss...
この国に隔離指定生物が 逃げ込んだかもしれない。
Unparalleled joy.
ここは　まだ ＮＧＬ国内ではないですからね。
What is this feeling?
外交業務として 主に情報交換に使用します。 国の中に 同じような施設はあるか？
From now on, call me Meruem...
当然 外から来られた方々による 持ち込みも 固く　お断りしております。
That is the name my mother gave me.
め…　眼鏡もですか？
I see...
はい　服　ベルト　靴　下着などに プラスチックや化学繊維
So this is...
冗談じゃないわよ ここで裸になれっていうの？ ご心配なく。 この上に 天然素材の商品がございます。
...unconditional love!
金　銀　整形の シリコーンゴムなどを有し この場で摘出不可能な方は 入国をお断りしております。
Having witnessed an absolute
being's death and rebirth, and having shared their own beings with the King, Pouf and Youpi had at last reached
残ったのは　この５人か…。
the pinnacle of their species...
The level of Queen.
直腸にカメラや携帯電話を 隠すのは当たり前。
It's clear that his strength has increased.
入国した後で訓練した動物に
He's even stronger now!
ノートパソコンを運ばせようとした方も いらっしゃいましたね。
Our bodies have helped the King...
全員　問題ありませんでした。
And become part of him. What an honor... What bliss!
お疲れさまでした さぁ　どうぞ　お通りください。
The King's heartbeat! The King's warmth!
ようこそ！　ＮＧＬへ。
We even share the King's thoughts!
よし　ハント開始だ。
...confused.
)
How do you feel?
) ((仮に　そんな生物が いたとしても
Should we return to the palace first?
大騒ぎするような人は この国にはいませんよ)) ((もしも 動物に襲われて死んでも
If you wish for more of that food,
we can provide it.
それは自然の生物としての 我々の寿命なわけです))
In a few minutes, my clones will arrive.
とにかく海岸線に沿って 集落を チェックして行くしかないね。
Then that taste was real.
多分　本体は この国でもないってことだよ。 ここの連中の言ってることが 本当だとしての話だけどな。
As I wandered through the light,
I heard someone call my name.
ずっと　ついて来てるね　あの２人。
Calling, "Meruem."
特殊言語地区や 未開の部族との交渉役とか 体のいいこと言ってるけど 監視だろ？　あの２人。
I do not know if that was a dream or reality.
まぁ　もともと ここの連中に何も期待はしてない。
I cannot remember why
俺の勘が言ってる。 「ここにいる」とな。
I am here.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
Meruem-sama... You've lost your memory?
ヒッ！ 動くんじゃねえぜ。 死んじまっても 責任とれないからな。
In fact, I am brimming with energy.
け…　獣の分際で 人間様に指図すんじゃねえ！
But my mind is hazy...
うるせぇ!! あっ…。
We sent our clones to scout the area.
はぁ…　やれやれ。 質問には　ちゃんと答えろって 親に教わらなかったか？
They are searching for remaining
enemies to dispose of—
うっ　うぅ…。 救えねえぜ　おっさん。
You may have my best interests in mind. But when you lie to me, you betray me.
ああ やっちまった？
So, I was eating you.
殺しちまったら 保存しておけねえだろ？
But we made the decision!
フン！　今日中に肉団子にして 女王様に差し出せばいいだろ。
What happened? Give me an explanation.
勘に障るんだよ　こういう野郎は。
Before we can do that,
I must ask you one question.
身の程ってものを知らねえ。
It appears that you recall
our former appearances.
コソコソ逃げ回るようなら かわいげがあるってもんさ。 ケッ！　昨日は逃げ回る子供を 後ろから撃ったじゃねえかよ。
Do you remember the day
we first began serving you?
俺に任せれば 餌が暴れることもなく
I do not.
スマートに捕獲できるのによ？
I recognized that you were my
Royal Guards Pouf and Youpi
「動くな」ってのは 俺に言ったんだよな？
the moment I saw you.
師団長の俺によ？　えっ？
No, I should say I remembered that you were.
あんまり 調子に乗るんじゃねえぜ？
Meruem-sama...
心の広い俺だから 大目に見てやってるんだぜ？
I believe you are suffering from temporary
memory loss due to the explosion.
そんなに殺しが好きなら 給餌部隊に志願したらどうだ？
Explosion? Yes.
救えねえ。
You came here to engage
in a duel with the enemy. However, the cowardly human
ユンジュの奴…　ん？
A duel...
うるせぇ！　黙らねえと 今すぐ食っちまうぜ！
fighting a duel.
ラモット！ ん？ 何してる？ 何って　獲物を運んでるんだよ 見りゃ分かるだろ。
We knew that, given your power and fortune, a mere human weapon could
never deal a lethal blow.
獲物は厳選しろ！ 何度も言わせるな！
However, we could not bear
to see you in that state.
そんなもの　何の足しにもならぬ。 それに　今日のノルマは終わった 運ぶだけ無駄。 だったら俺が食ってやるよ。 何？
So we did what we could to speed your recovery, knowing full well that we might be punished.
どうせ　いつかは 食われちまうんだ。
Our bodies have always been yours.
これは命令だ！　ラモット。
We were simply returning them to you. Let's return to the palace!
グゥ…。 へっ。
That will be the fastest way
for you to regain your memory!
まったく 勝手な奴らが増えて困る。
This is my perfect
えっ？　別に　いいんだよ 俺は好きでやってんだから。
I can dispose of her! At the moment, the King does not remember her.
何なら　これ持ってくか？ 死んでるからダメか…。 お前ら　どこの部隊だっけ？ ギギ。 えっ？
If I eliminate her now, he will never have the chance to remember her!
ギガガ。
This will require...
あぁ　ザザンか あの　いけ好かない女のとこね。
Convincing Pitou? Getting rid of that meddling human?
同情するぜ。 ギジュ…　ギギ。 じゃあ　ユンジュ隊の所にでも 行ってみるか？
No... The first thing to do
あそこの部隊は 人間を好き放題　殺せるらしいぜ。
is to end her life.
手土産持参で行きゃあ　すぐに 入隊できるんじゃねえか？
If I kill her, everything else will fall into place.
何だよ　こりゃ。 ひどい。 一体　誰が…。
I have enough time to kill her.
こいつらは ディーディーを密造している ＮＧＬの裏の連中だ。 えっ？
This feels as natural as though
I was born with these.
この傷… とても人間技とは思えない。
I will learn to fly in no time.
これが その化け物の仕業だとしたら
Which way to the palace?
このメンバーでは とても太刀打ちできないだろう
North. You should be able to make
it in fifteen minutes!
俺が合図をしたら逃げろ。
It's there.
いいな。
The answer I seek is in the palace.
救えねえ。
I have but two to three minutes.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…！
Quickly, my clones! This is a gamble.
あっ！ キャ!! あっ！ あっ…　あぁ…。
Once the King sees the millions
of humans outside the palace, he will remember everything!
あっ　あぁ…　あぁ…。
Remember that his objective
is to rule all living creatures!
こっちだ！
So long as he doesn't see that woman!
大丈夫か？ ええ。 とりあえず　他のプロハンターに 連絡をとろう。
I must eliminate that lowly human girl!
頼む　ポンズ。 分かったわ。
She's gone!
いや　まだ　おりますわ。
Before I was placed in the cocoon.
いるいる！　におうわ！ 生きた人間のにおい！
So I can see you, no matter where you are.
ハッハッハッハ…！
What? What just attacked my clone?
どうする？　ザイカハル。
It seems to have resulted from the
remaining enemies attacking my clone.
風雲急を告げるＮＧＬ ゴン達は今　その真っただ中に
The King!